给我20块
For 20 bucks,
我就告诉你上周的《无耻家庭》发生了什么
I'll tell you what happened last week on Shameless.
谢谢
Thanks.
你得去做人流
You're gonna have to have an abortion.
才不要  我才不要打掉我的孩子
Hell, no. I'm not aborting my baby.
我们的孩子
Our baby.
你得给家里打个电话
You need to call your family.
你爸快死了  伊恩
Your dad's dying, Ian.
操  伊恩
Fuck. Ian.
我们只剩下两个孩子了
We're down to two babies.
-怎么回事  -休伊吃了杜威
- What happened? - Huey ate dewey.
-你差点害死利亚姆  -我不是故意的
- You almost killed Liam. - I didn't do it on purpose.
-但你还是做了  -我没罪
- Yeah, but you did it. - I'm not guilty!
利亚姆差点死了
Liam almost died!
今早在校车上听到你们
I heard you talk about my little brother Liam
谈论我弟利亚姆了
on the bus this morning.
可卡因小弟
Cocaine baby brother.
操
Oh, fuck.
我可以帮你看利亚姆
I could watch Liam for you if you wanted.
我半小时给你发一张照片
I'll send you a text picture every 30 minutes.
-我需要把枪  -你想毙了谁
- I need a gun. - Who you gonna kill?
艾莱柏被劫了
Alibi got robbed.
他们偷了我放钱的酒桶
They stole the keg that I keep the money in.
我们不能做男女朋友
We can't be boyfriend and girlfriend.
那为什么要跟我分手
Why are you breaking up with me?
因为你太小了
Because you're too young.
快点给我滚出去
Get the fuck out of my house.
希拉会不会生我的气
Is Sheila gonna be mad at me?
她出城了
She's out of town.
只要你认罪
With this plea agreement,
你会成为一名重罪犯
you will be a felon.
你将被软禁在家  等待后续通知
You will be under house arrest until further notice.
你承认自己犯下藏毒罪
How do you plead to possession
以及危害儿童罪吗
and child endangerment?
我承认
I'm guilty.
无耻家庭
第四季第八集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：  猛回头     重案组李Sir     落     君君
■
翻译：  青椒     爱卿遛小鸟     拉图     Greentie
时间轴：  大喷子      浓子
■
校对：  Greentie      落
后期： 孤帆          总监： 落
■
破处倒计时
2014年7月  我的14岁生日
2015年12月  还有一年半
2015年7月  还有一年
2016年  再熬六个月
最后三个月
还差一点点
要熬到头了
超热辣性爱
童贞再见
为爱着魔
调情圣手
舌尖
你有没有卫生巾
Do you have any sanitary pads?
你来月经啦  太棒了
You got your period? That's wonderful.
我不想聊这个  永远不想
I don't want to talk about it. Ever.
我懂  我懂
I get it. I get it.
家里有卫生棉条
We have some tampons
在楼上浴室的洗脸台下面
in the upstairs bathroom under the sink.
要我教你怎么...
Do you need me to walk you through any--
不  不用了
No. Nope.
你干嘛早上七点就做饼干
Why are you baking at 7:00 a.m.?
今天我的假释官要来
'Cause my probation officer's coming today
我很紧张  你房间干净吗
and I'm freaking out. Is your room clean?
这关我房间干净不干净什么事
Why does my room need to be clean?
因为她会把这地方翻个底朝天
'Cause she's gonna tear the joint apart
寻找任何不该出现的东西
looking for anything that can get me in trouble.
我房间只有衣服  学校的东西和化妆品
I only have, like, clothes and school stuff and makeup.
小黛  就当帮我个忙  行吗
Debs, just do me this one favor, okay?
我不能冒险
I can't take any chances.
又不是我把可卡因放在外面的
Well, I'm not the one who left the cocaine out.
去整理
Do it.
老天
God.
闪开
Get out.
我饿了
Hungry.
这里有半袋麦片
We have half a bag of cereal,
两包燕麦粥  四张冰冻华夫饼
two packs of oatmeal, and four frozen waffles.
你上学前得先把房间整理干净
You need to clean your room before school.
把该扔的扔了  别让人觉得我是个不称职的家长
Get rid of anything that can make me look like a bad parent.
现在就去
Go. Now.
这是给假释官的
Those are for my PO.
上楼去
Upstairs.
你死了没
Are you dead?
才没有
Not a chance.
说到哪儿了
Where were we?
第九条  抢劫一家便利店
Number 9, rob a convenience store.
第十条  回收废金属
Number 10, recycle scrap metal.
十一条  做鸭
Number 11, prostitution.
这条删掉
Nix that one.
我的动力钻现在动不了了
My thrill drill is out of juice.
这是开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me!
十二条  捐精
Number 12, sperm bank.
同十一条
See number 11.
有个叫什么法希德·艾米德·哈比博的酋长
Some sheik named Fahid Ahmed Habib or whatever
获得了一对新的肺
is getting a brand-new set of lungs.
政府给他插队了
Government flew him in.
我们家订报纸了吗
We get the newspaper?
希拉订的
Sheila does.
你看
Look. Look.
和外科医生握手
Shaking hands with his surgeon.
某些混蛋能插队
Some towelhead gets to jump the line
就因为他是所谓的"重要伙伴"
just 'cause he's a "Important Ally?"
这家伙有八个未成年的老婆  只给她们穿桌布
Guy's got eight teenage wives dressed in tableoths.
连车都不让她们开
Won't even let 'em drive.
听着  萨咪
Look, Sammi.
恰奇和我想要...
Chuckie and I are trying--
我们正在写...
We're--we're writing--
算了  给她看吧  小恰
Ah, fuck it. Show her, Chuckles.
绑架一个沃尔顿家族的人[世上最富有家族]
Kidnap a Walton heir.
路边摆摊卖水果
Roadside fruit stand.
职业杀手
Contract killer.
这是什么
What are these?
攒钱做手术的法子
Ways to make money for my surgery.
把我的书做成APP怎么样
What about an app version of my book?
就是我那本百毒宝典
The drug book that I'm writing?
要怀着希望嘛  对吧
Got to keep hope alive, right?
放轻松  爸爸
Easy, honey.
这是奥施康定和氨酚羟考酮
Here's your oxys and your perkies.
我妈以前也这么弄
Just like mama used to make.
真的很臭
Whoa, that is bad.
对麦麸过敏的家伙们
Okay, all you glu-tards in the house,
不含小麦的烙饼做好了
wheat-free flapjacks are ready.
趁热吃吧
Get them while they suck.
嘿  小家伙
Hey, short-stack!
击个掌
High five.
这孩子怎么了  菲尔
What's up with your kid, Phil?
怎么这么淡定
Why's he so damn calm?
脑部受损
Brain damage.
必须告诉你
Gotta tell you, man,
我没想到带孩子上班居然可行
I didn't think this was gonna work out.
-是啊  -真可爱
- Yeah. - Adorable.
是你的孩子吗
He yours?
不  是我弟弟
No, brother.
因为家长都是混蛋
Deadbeat parents and so on.
所以由你照顾他吗
Aw, so you take care of him?
是  我尽力而为吧
Yeah. Yeah, no. I do my best.
厉害
Cool.
那么  请享用美食吧
So enjoy.
你有不用照顾他的时候吗
Ever get a break from watching him?
当然  偶尔有的
Sure, yeah. Sometimes.
我明早有空
I'm free tomorrow morning.
11点左右
Around 11.
好极了
Great.
再见
Bye.
您想要什么  先生
Hey, what can I get you, sir?
天呐  卡尔
Jesus Christ, Carl
走开  屋里没有毒品  酒和枪
怎么了  黛布拉
Yes, Debra?
我能去趟厕所吗
Can I use the bathroom?
又要去
Again?
女生的私事啦
Girl stuff.
卧室都是干净的
So the bedrooms are all clean.
还有谁住在这里
Who else lives in the house?
我的两个弟弟  卡尔和利亚姆
My two brothers, Carl and Liam,
我妹妹  黛比
my sister, Debbie,
有时候我弟弟利普也回来住
and sometimes my brother Lip.
-他们都比你小  -是的
- All younger? - Yes.
他们会帮助你改过自新吗
Will they help you not re-offend?
当然  我是他们的监护人
Well, yeah. I'm their guardian.
你的家人知晓你所犯的罪吗
Is the family fully aware of the crime committed?
知道
Oh, yes.
你有出于任何理由
Do you have plans
-要离开伊利诺伊州吗  -没有
- to leave the state of Illinois for any reason? - No.
你有藏有枪支
Are you in possession
-或危险武器吗  -没有
- of any firearms or dangerous weapons? - No.
你与任何能诱导你
Are you in contact with anyone who might cause you
-吸毒跟酗酒的人联系吗  -没有
- to engage in drug and alcohol abuse? - No.
你还有其他家人
Is anyone else in the household
有违法行为吗
in trouble with the law?
没有
Uh, no.
这个家里的没有
Not-- not in the household.
你每天问这些问题一定很烦了
You must get tired of asking these questions every day.
来块饼干吗
Do you want a cookie?
我自己烤的
I baked them myself.
如果把原料从管子里挤出来算"自己烤"的话
If you consider squeezing batter from a tube "baking."
我不是你的朋友
Look, I'm not your friend.
我是来确保你没有违反
I'm here to make sure you don't violate
你的假释条件
the terms of your probation.
好的
Right.
我什么时候能出门找工作
So when can I get out of here and start looking for a job?
我是这家里唯一的经济来源  现在资金比较紧张
I'm the sole earner, and money's pretty tight.
报告批下来之前你不能出去
You can't leave the house until a report is filed.
需要多长时间
And how long does that take?
-五至十个工作日  -两周
- Five to ten business days. - Two weeks?
有时能快点  但是希望不大
Sometimes quicker, but I wouldn't count on it.
我要是出去会怎样
What happens if I leave?
这东西会  爆炸吗
Does this thing, like, detonate?
如果你企图离开这里
If you attempt to leave the residence,
无线电波发射器会给我们警局的电脑中心
a radio-frequency transmitter will send an alert
发送警报  然后你  菲奥娜小姐
to our service computer center and you, Miss Fiona,
麻烦就大了
will be in deep shit.
我需要一份尿样
I need a urine sample
来检查你有没有吸毒
so that I can test your system for drugs.
没问题
No problem.
我得看着
And I need to watch.
什么
What?
看我尿尿
Me pissing?
确保是你的尿样
To be sure it's yours.
相信我  我比你还不乐意
Believe me, I enjoy this even less than you do.
你得先擦一下
You need to wipe first.
早上好
Morning.
是下午了
It is afternoon.
你睡了一整天
You sleep all day.
我马上要生了
I have baby soon.
-我不能工作  -我去
- I can not work. - Jeez.
他必须照顾我跟孩子
He must take care of me and baby.
你滚
You go.
我们不需要你
We do not need you.
你今晚在这里住
You sleep here tonight in this house?
我就杀了你
I kill you.
把你的橘子头给你拍扁
I bash your orange head.
什么
What?
不是吧
No!
-过来  -天呐
- Come here. - Oh, my God.
我的天呐  这是真的吗
Oh, my God, is this for real?
你真的回来了
Are you really back?
真的  暂时的
For real. For now.
天呐  你个混蛋  我想死你了
Oh, my god, you bastard, I missed you so much.
你这个混蛋  你让我担心死了
You're a piece of shit. You had me so worried.
-一通电话都不打  -我发短信了
- Not one call? - I texted.
是啊  太详细了
Yeah. Real detailed.
"想你们  我很好"
"Miss you guys, having fun."
我不想让你担心
I didn't want you to worry.
我更担心了  混蛋
Well, I worried more, asshole.
你去哪了
Where the hell were you?
部队  我参军了
The army. I enlisted.
-参军了  -是的
- The army? - Yeah.
想寻找一下自我
I wanted to find myself.
觉得在这里寻找不到
Didn't think I could do it here.
不是要18岁才可以吗
Don't you have to be 18?
不知道  也不在意
Don't know, don't care.
我离开了  事情失控了
I left. Stuff got nuts.
什么事情
What "stuff?"
军队想要控制我
Oh, military trying to control me.
军队不就是控制人的地方吗
Well, isn't that what the military does?
受够了  但是也认识了不少很棒的小伙伴
Got sick of it, but, hey, I met some amazing folks.
三观被正了
Got all these great ideas.
现在这是个全新的我
I'm a different person.
我们可以晚点再聊这个  对吧
Hey, but we can talk about that later, right?
当然
Sure.
你想吃三明治吗
Do you want a sandwich?
当然  饿死了
Yeah! Oh, starving.
给你吃吧
It's yours.
设备不错
Nice hardware.
是啊
Huh, yeah.
棉靴都穿不进去了
My winter boots don't fit.
我能穿的只有磨脚的高跟鞋跟网球鞋
All I can get on are fuck-me pumps and tennis shoes.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
很好  非常棒  怎么了
Yeah. Yeah, great, why?
你看起来有点像咖啡因过量
You seem a little caffeinated.
我戒烟了
I quit smoking.
你接下来要做什么
So what's next for you?
我在考虑给我遇到的
Oh, I've been thinking about apprenticing
一个电工当学徒
with this electrician I met.
学学电线什么的
You know, learn how to wire stuff.
不念高中了吗
What about high school?
弗兰克念完高中了
Oh, well, Frank finished high school.
他混得真不错
It worked out great for him.
你必须念完  伊恩
You have to finish, Ian--
我不用必须做任何事
I don't have to do anything.
我受够了按别人说的生活了
I'm done living the way other people want me to live.
但是谢谢你的三明治
But, hey, thanks for the sandwich.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
这是个好家伙
Yeah, it's a nice little piece, you know.
反应快  不卡子弹
Quick to action, doesn't jam.
小心点  宝贝
Easy, baby.
你当下还有什么武器
What else you packing?
什么意思  是说"裆下武器"吗
What do you mean, like, dick-wise?
不是  我是说这不是你唯一的武器  是吧
No. I mean, that's not your only weapon, is it?
一个人需要几把枪
Well, how many guns does a guy need?
看情况
Well, it depends.
如果你要制造安全的假象
If you want to create the illusion of safety,
那一把就够了
then one piece is plenty.
但是如果你真的想要
But if you really want to be ready
武装起来应对紧急情况
in the event of an emergency,
你要再进一步
you'll need to step it up.
每个屋子里放一把
One for every room in the house.
车里放一把
One for your car.
工作的地方放一把
One at work.
身上至少带两把
And at least two on your person.
你有几把枪
How many guns do you own?
我有一把毒蛇AR15
Um, I got a bushmaster AR15,
一把HK USP45   还有格洛克23  40 CAL
an HK USP .45,  Glock 23 .40 CAL,
9毫米的西格萨奥P224R
my Sig Sauer p226r 9-millimeter,
一把点22亨利
a Henry .22 magnum,
一把鲁格101左轮
A ruger sp101 3-inch six-shot,
还有瓦尔特P22
and my walther p22.
我认识一个人
I know a guy.
可以介绍给你
I can hook you up.
我的格言就是
My motto is prepare and prevent,
早作准备  免得后悔莫及
don't repair and repent.
搞什么  你们以为来度假的吗
The hell is this, poolside at the Flamingo?
楼上的客人都饥渴难耐了
We got a line of clients upstairs
排着队等你们呢
with their hands down their pants.
赶紧开工了
Go to work.
还有你  别以为有孩子要从
And you, don't think you're getting off
你那毛茸茸的下体出来  就可以偷懒
just 'cause you're about to drop a patty from your fur-burger.
-"毛茸茸"  -她不刮毛
- "Fur-burger?" - She won't shave.
-我就喜欢自然的样子  -那好吧
- I like the way god made me. - That's nice.
你要再迟到我就扣你50块
You're late again, I'm gonna dock you 50.
-红毛小子走了  -红毛小子是谁
- Carrot boy is gone. - Who's carrot boy?
-他心里清楚  -他去哪儿了
- He knows who. - Where'd he go?
不知道  我把他赶走了
I don't know. I made him leave.
马上要生了  没地方给他住
No room for him when baby comes.
又他妈不关我事
The fuck do I care?
赶紧去刮你的毛
And shave your fucking muff.
老师要我来办公室找她
Teacher told me to come down to the office.
我真希望我可以说
I wish I could say
很高兴再见到你  加拉格先生
it's a pleasure to see you again, Mr. Gallagher.
你的杰作
Your handiwork?
没什么  小意思
I don't want to brag.
你有麻烦了
We have a problem.
有麻烦的是他们  手无缚鸡之力
They're the ones with the problem. Can't fight for shit.
为什么你们欺负他们
Why did you assault all these students?
他们说我弟坏话
Talkin' smack about my brother.
全部吗
All of them?
那个发型特傻逼
And that one's got stupid hair.
那个全身散发恶臭
And that one smells like bologna farts.
被你用柜门夹了手的那个呢
And the one whose hand you smashed in a locker?
还有被你推下楼梯的那个
And the one you pushed down the stairs?
可能因为太矮了吧
Too short, maybe?
我忘了
I don't remember.
你被停学了
You're hereby suspended from school.
周五早上8点
8 am Friday morning, you will come back
带你的家长或监护人一起来
with a parent or guardian and you will apologize
给这些孩子还有他们的父母道歉
to all these children in the presence of their parents
否则就一直让你停学
or your suspension will last indefinitely.
-什么意思  -开除的意思
- Which means? - Expulsion.
开除是什么意思
Which means?
回家吧  卡尔
Go home, Carl.
到时候和家长一起来
Come back with a parent.
等不及看看是谁教出你这样的坏分子
I can't wait to see who created you.
我明天11点半第一节课
My first class tomorrow is at 11:30,
所以今晚住在这儿
so we're gonna stay here tonight,
周五的课是早上8点
and then Friday it's 8:00 am.
所以明晚住宿舍
So we're gonna stay at the dorms tomorrow night.
知道了  知道了
Got it. Got it.
坐好了
There we go.
我的小宝贝儿
Hi, my big boy.
想我了吗
Did you miss me today?
真的想吗
Oh, you did?
我也想你
I missed you too.
你带晚饭了  太好了
Oh, you brought dinner. That's great.
那就可以把今晚的芝士通心粉留到明天吃
That means we can move tonight's mac and cheese to tomorrow,
又可以少担心一天食物
which gives us an extra day of food before we panic.
担心
Panic?
我买吃的之前得先把暖气费和电费交了
I got to pay the heat and electric before I buy groceries.
现在冷死了
It's pretty bleak.
公司的支票马上就来了
I got a check coming from the cups,
但那钱要用来付房租
but that's gonna cover rent, and food-wise,
吃方面只能靠通心粉和蛋黄酱过日子了
we're low on everything but macaroni and mayonnaise.
你之前都没存钱吗
You saved nothing from your job?
之前的钱都用来还旧账了
I was trying to catch up on old bills.
-他今天还好吗  -挺好的
- How'd he do today? - Yeah, he's fine.
-卡尔被停学了  -什么
- Carl got suspended. - What?
闭嘴  白痴
Shut up, ass-brain.
-利普  -小鬼  你好吗
- Hi, Lip. - Hey, kiddo, how are ya?
兄弟
Hey, bud.
周五早上得有人陪我去学校
I need someone to go to school with me Friday morning
不然他们会开除我
or I'll be expelled.
我还不能离开屋子
Well, I can't leave the house yet.
得让他们换个时间
They need to reschedule.
-你没告诉他们我不能出门吗  -没
- Did you tell them I'm stuck at home? - No.
明天去告诉他们我病了
Well, go in tomorrow and tell them I'm sick.
得了疱疹什么的
I have shingles or mono.
我陪你去  几点
I'll take you, bruiser. What time?
-早上八点  -不行  我有课
- 8 am. - Oh, fuck. I got class.
能稍微晚点吗  中午行不行
Can you make it a little later, like, around noon?
不行  其他家长也会去
No, parents will be there and stuff.
大家好
Hi, new family.
门没锁
Door was open.
我马上就走
I won't stay long,
就是来告诉你们  老爸在希拉家
just wanted to let you know, dad's at Sheila's house.
我们暂时住在那儿  真是个好地方
We're living there a bit. It's a really great place.
房间多  又敞亮
Plenty of room, lots of light.
多谢告知
Thanks for the update.
你们手头有钱吗
Any of you guys have any extra cash?
老爸需要钱动手术
Dad wants money for his surgery.
你怎么不去上班挣钱
Why not get a job?
现在我要全身心的照顾老爸
Right now, my full-time career is taking care of our pops
在他归西之前
before he goes.
我们破产了
Well, we're broke.
真可惜帮不到你
Wish we could help you.
没关系  问问总无妨
Okay. Doesn't hurt to ask.
如果有谁想过来  给他打打气
If anyone wants to stop by, give his morale a boost,
信念可以治病
hope can heal.
信念可以补偿
Oh, yeah, can hope make up
他以前带给我们的痛苦时光吗
for the years of misery that he put us through?
也许吧  有空过来
Maybe. Come by.
看看行不行
Find out.
他不该就这么离世
He doesn't deserve to go out like this.
任何人都不该
No one does.
怎么不叫弗兰克陪你去学校  卡尔
Why not ask Frank to go to school with you, Carl?
伊恩在吗
Ian here?
他在楼上
He's upstairs.
伊恩回来了
Ian's here?
你就这么收拾东西走了
See you left. Took all your shit.
你老婆拿锤子威胁我
Your bride threatened me with a claw hammer.
-你回来了  -你们好
- You're back! - Oh, hey, guys.
我想死你们了
Oh, man. I missed you guys.
兄弟  过来
Hey, man. Come here.
利普说你偷了架直升机
Lip says you stole a helicopter.
想偷来着
I tried to.
差不多吧
Kind of tipped it.
启动了引擎  螺旋桨都转了
Blades snapped. Motor caught fire.
酷毙了  你杀人了吗
Awesome. You shoot anyone?
我一直呆在新兵营
I never left basic.
那里不能杀人吗
You can't shoot anyone there?
可以  但我没有
You can. I didn't.
又没杀人  又没开到飞机
You shot no one. You flew nothing.
那你干嘛去参军
Why'd you even go there in the first place?
感情问题
Relationship issues.
你还好吗
Yeah, you okay?
-挺好的  -那就好
- Yup, all good. - Cool.
下楼吃饭吧
All right. Well, let's go get some dinner, dorks.
我等下再和你聊
Hey, I'll catch up with you later, yeah?
-一会儿见  -好
- Yeah, later, man. - All right.
-走了  白痴  -去吧
- Come on, dork - Go.
你打算回来吗
You coming back?
看情况
Depends.
你愿意随时吃我的鸡巴吗
Will you suck my dick whenever I want?
滚蛋
Fuck off.
-你在写什么  -东西
- What you writing? - Stuff.
想法什么的
Notes, ideas.
我愿意
I'll do it.
愿意什么
Do what?
别逼我说出来  混蛋
Don't make me say it, asswipe.
吃我的鸡巴
Suck my dick.
无论我何时想要
Whenever I want.
豌豆
Peas.
我想到一个主意
I thought of something.
说具体点
Be specific.
我们可以把房子卖了
We could sell the house.
-哪个房子  -就这个  希拉的房子
- Which house? - This one. Sheila's.
我们没有所有权  小宝贝
We don't have the title. Sweet potatoes.
不需要啊
Don't need it.
我们在外放个出售牌
We put a sign out front,
写一个比市价低很多的数目
offer way below market,
让有意的买家用现金付定
have people make cash offers for earnest money.
搞定  然后重复
Wash, rinse, repeat.
定金  小钱不管用
"Earnest money"? Lentils.
他们可以给售价的3%
They give us 3% of the purchase price,
我们保证不再挂牌出售了
we say we'll take it off the market.
当然了  我们不会真那样做
We don't, of course.
我们拿走那部分现金就好
We just grab the cash.
持续这样做四五次  筹到大约1.1万块
Do this four or five times, rake in maybe 11 grand.
小钱也感激万分
Christ on a crumb bun.
我知道的啦
I know, right?
肯定比不上什么让人振奋的大计谋
Nothing like a major scam to life a person's spirits.
你是怎么知道这些诡计的
How do you know all this?
我以前这么做过一两次
I may have done this once or twice before
和那么一两任丈夫一起干的
with one or more husbands.
你真不愧是加拉格家的人
You really are a Gallagher.
然后我的教官直接冲进我的房门
So then my TI comes crashing through my door, right,
然后开始追我
and chases me.
我害怕极了
I'm so scared,
我直接撞到了一个饮水器上
I run smack into a water fountain,
把它从墙上撞掉下来了
bust it right off the wall.
-什么  -没错  我知道  水喷得到处都是
- What? - Yeah, I know. Water sprays everywhere.
然后他凌晨2点把大家都叫醒了
And he wakes everyone up at 2:00 a.m. in the morning,
强迫他们看我在冰冷的水中
forces them to watch me do pushups
一边做俯卧撑一边唱歌
in the freezing cold water while singing.
唱歌
Singing?
*然后是哼哼哈嘿*
*Well, then it's hi, hi, hey *
*大兵行军忙*
*The army's on its way *
*高声把那军歌唱*
*Count off the cadence loud and strong *
*二三  无论你去到哪儿*
*Two, three, for wherever you go *
*你都会知道*
*You will always know *
*大兵行军忙*
*That the army goes marching along *
一切都还好吗
Everything okay?
你还在上学吗
Still in school?
是的
Yeah.
事情都  算是在正轨上吧
Yeah, it's, um, it's under control.
米奇在这儿吗
Is Mickey here?
是的  他在楼上  怎么了
Yeah, he's upstairs. Why?
你们家人一大早的总是这么吵吗
You always so goddamn noisy in the morning?
怎么了
What?
你老婆的羊水破了
Your wife's water broke.
-我们走吧  -去哪儿
- Let's go. - Go where?
-医院  -她要生孩子了吗
- The hospital. - She's having the baby?
跟她说我祝她好运
Tell her I said good luck.
怎么  你不去陪她吗
What, you're not gonna go be with her?
当然不去了  我得工作
Hell, no. I got work.
你们关系烂  又不是宝宝的错
It's not the baby's fault you guys are a shit show.
是啊  但那个贱人被搞大肚子
Yeah, and it's not my fault
也不是我的错
the bitch got knocked up.
谁他妈知道那个孩子到底是不是我的
Who the fuck knows if it's even mine?
你真是个混蛋
You're an asshole.
恭喜
Congrats.
满满一家人  跟过去一样
Full house, like old times.
闻起来真香  是昨天的剩菜吗
Smells good. Leftovers?
你毁了我的艺术作业
You destroyed my art project.
彻底毁了
It's completely ruined.
你真是个大贱人
You're such a bitch!
黛比
Debbie!
她跑进我的房间
She went into my room,
把我的东西都毁了
she trashed all of my stuff,
然后把我所有的衣服都踢到了床下
and she kicked all of my clothes under the bed.
-我提醒过你清扫了  -有吗
- I asked you to clean up. - Did you?
她也翻了我的东西
She went through mine too.
她把我的黄片都扔了
She threw away my porn,
以及双截棍和电击枪
my nunchucks, and my taser.
你知道我翻了多少警局垃圾箱
You know how many police dumpsters
才找到那些的吗
I had to go through to find that?
我早叫你扔掉那些东西了
I told you to get rid of that stuff.
我藏起来了  那该死的假释官就不会发现了
I hid it so the stupid P.O. wouldn't find it.
幸运的是  你那愚蠢的姐姐先发现了
Well, luckily, your stupid sister found it first.
天啊  或许下次你们就该听我的  你们都是
God, maybe next time you'll do what I ask, both of you.
午餐是通心粉沙拉三明治
There's macaroni salad sandwiches for lunch.
-多加了蛋黄酱  -不需要
- Extra mayo. - Don't need it.
-我被停学了  -那你还是得吃饭啊
- I'm suspended. - Well, you still need to eat.
我们出门了
Look, we're gonna get out of here, okay?
我们今晚会回来吃晚饭
We'll be back for dinner tonight.
利普  你可以把利亚姆留在家里的
Well, Lip, you can leave Liam here.
-我可以照顾他  -不  利普
- I got him. - No, Lip.
听着  菲奥娜  你好好睡一觉好吗
Look, Fiona, just get some sleep, okay?
跟小维一起玩玩
Hang out with V.
放松  拜托了
Relax, for fuck's sake.
如果发生什么事  记得发短信给我好吗
You guys text me if anything's going on, okay?
-好的  当然了  -走吧  卡尔
- Yeah, sure. - Come on, Carl. Let's go.
-你要去哪儿  -去希拉家
- Where are you going? - To Sheila's.
为什么
Why?
看看弗兰克明天能不能陪我去学校
To see if Frank can take me to school tomorrow morning.
你什么时候回来
Well, when will you be back?
晚些时候  别烦我了
Later. Get off my ass.
再见  伊恩
Bye, Ian.
再见  小黛
Bye, Debs.
要再来一些吗
Want some more?
你有现金能给一点我吗
You got any cash you could toss my way?
我今晚要轮两个班
I'm working a double tonight.
-你想过来探班吗  -好啊
- You want to stop by? - Yeah, sure.
没有什么能比看着一帮傻逼基佬
Got nothing better to do than watch a bunch of pruney queens
用蛋蛋顶着你的屁股更有意思了
slap their sacks against your ass cheeks.
该死
Shit!
喂  等一下
Hey! Guys!
嗨  希拉给我留了一把钥匙
Hi, um, Sheila left me a key.
我很高兴你能来  欢迎
I'm so glad you came. Welcome.
我是来给盆栽浇水的
Supposed to water the plants.
为什么门前挂着一个"此房出售"的牌子
Why is there a for sale sign out front?
爸  黛比和卡尔来了
Dad, Debbie and Carl are here.
你明天早上能陪我去学校吗
Can you come with me to school tomorrow morning?
那我得取消早晨的单车健身课了  怎么了
Have to cancel my morning spin class. What's up?
我因为霸凌同学被停学了
I got suspended for bullying.
必须带家长去学校道歉
Need a parent to come with me to apologize.
道...
Apo--
太过分了
Outrageous.
给我打了麻醉剂
Feed me numbing agents
竟然还要拉我出去
and drag me to the ring.
你这个样子不能去任何地方
You are in no shape to go anywhere.
他必须去  不然我就会被开除
He needs to or else I'll get expelled.
我很抱歉  卡尔  他太虚弱了
I'm so sorry, Carl, but he's too weak.
能借我一件长毛衣吗
Could I borrow a long sweater?
当然了  宝贝  给
Of course, honey. Here.
谢谢
Thanks.
你还需要别的什么吗
Do you need anything else?
好吧
Oh, okay.
卡尔  如果你拿些气球
Carl, if you grab those balloons
绑到前门的出售牌上
and tie them to the sign out front,
我就让你玩玩我的枪
I'll let you hold my gun.
我月经来了  但菲奥娜只有卫生棉条
I got my period, but all Fiona has are tampons
我想保住处女之身  直到我真正变成一个女人
and I'm saving my virginity until I become a woman.
好吧  首先
Okay, first of all,
使用卫生棉条  不会失去处女之身
you can't lose your virginity to a tampon.
必须是男人的阴茎插入才算失身
It has to be a penis with a man attached.
其次  你已经是个女人了
And second, you're already a woman.
正式的了
Officially.
从大姨妈叩响你的"大门"那刻起就是了
From the moment aunt flo came knocking at your vagina.
那我男朋友为什么还非要等到我16岁
Then why won't my boyfriend have sex with me
才肯跟我做爱
until I'm 16?
现在居然还有这样的人
They still make them like that?
你男朋友是好人
You got a good one.
卫生棉是大人用的
Tampons are varsity level,
你还小
and you are still J.V.
给  用这些吧
Here, try these.
谢谢
Thanks.
我今晚能在这里过夜吗
Could I stay here tonight?
当然可以了
I love a sleepover.
住下吧
Absolutely.
喂  怎么啦
Hey, what's up?
是这样  我想把垃圾扔出去
Uh, listen, I'm trying to take the trash out.
你能过来帮帮我吗
Could you come help?
当然  还需要其他的吗
Sure. You need anything else?
能给我来一加仑伏特加吗
How about a gallon of vodka?
好  我20分钟后到
All right, I'll be there in 20 minutes.
谢了
Thanks.
有乐高积木  土豆头先生[玩具总动员]
So we have legos, Mr. Potato head,
恐龙  玩具车
dinosaurs, cars.
给他吃奇多玉米片之前
Make sure he eats at least half his pb&j
先让他吃半块以上的花生酱三明治
before you give him his cheetos,
他今天还没拉屎
and he hasn't pooped today,
不过他一般会抓着屁股吼一声"粑粑炸弹"
but he'll usually grab his butt and yell "Doody bomb!"
算是给你一点提示
so you'll have fair warning.
还有什么  对了
What else-- Oh.
看好他的蜡笔
Keep an eye on his crayons.
他经常会往自己鼻子上乱画
He likes to jam them up his nose.
好的  明白了
Okay, got it.
这小孩简直是白马王子
This kid, total dreamboat.
我男人要是有他一半魅力就好了
The men in my life should be half as charming.
包里有创可贴  擦屁股纸
Okay, then we got band-aids, butt wipes--
当然少不了他的玩具猴
Oh, stuffed monkey, of course.
两个弹球  两副拼图  还有几只河马玩具
Two bouncy balls, two puzzles, very hungry hippos,
这还有体温计和儿童用泰诺止痛药
and then we've got a thermometer and then children's tylenol,
以防万一他发烧什么的
you know, just in case he gets a fever.
好的  你要离开多久
Okay, how long are you gonna be gone for?
三个小时  不过你知道的
Oh, three hours, but, you know,
就怕万一嘛
you can't be too careful.
你真是个好人
You're a really good person.
不  我要是个好人的话
No, if I were a really good person,
就会退学  待在家里全职照顾他
then I would quit school and I'd stay home full time.
那样也没什么好处的
Well, who does that help?
也对
Right. Um...
我2点就回来了
Okay, so I'll be back at 2:00.
应该没问题吧
Is that still cool?
别忘了今天晚上宿舍有ABC派对
Don't forget about the abc party tonight at the dorm.
-什么  -你知道的
- What's that? - Oh, you know.
"除了衣服什么可以"
"Anything but clothes."
胶带  警告带  垃圾袋  床单
Duct tape, caution tape, trash bags, bedsheets.
好吧  我明天有个文学论文要交
Okay, well, I got a lit paper due tomorrow,
不过派对听起来很有趣
but that sounds fun.
给你  谢谢你这么帮我
Here you go. And thank you so much for doing all this.
真的  我不知道该怎么报答你
You know, I wish I could think of a way to repay you.
我相信你会想到的
I'm sure you'll think of something.
-久等了  -你来了
- Hey. Hi. - Hey.
我11点半要去实验室
So, uh, I got a lab at half-past,
所以大概只有20分钟
so I only got, like, 20 minutes.
没事  我很快的
That's okay. I'm quick.
好吧  还有就是
Right, and also
我最近生活一团糟
I'm kind of going through some shit,
所以可能不想...
so I'm not really looking for anything too, uh--
兄弟  我很冷  也很饥渴  别墨迹了
Dude, I'm cold, I'm horny, let's do this.
行  是去你的洗衣间还是我的
Okay. Uh, so your laundry room or mine?
上下  动起来
Up and down, come on!
燃烧所有脂肪
Let's burn the fat.
屁股甩起来
Swing that booty!
跟着芭菲健身
With Figure Eight fitness,
我减掉了9.5公斤
I lost a total 21 pounds.
我的腰部瘦了19厘米
I've lost 7 1/2 inches around my waist
减掉了24公斤
and 53 pounds.
我减了6.8公斤...
I've lost 15--
你他妈来这里干什么
The fuck are you doing here?
给你带了点小礼物
I brought you a little gift.
甜甜圈  我排了好长的队才买到
Cronuts. I stood online 40 minutes for those.
-还只能买两个  -你想干什么
- Only let me have two. - What do you want?
想先吃点点心
A trendy hybrid pastry for starts.
麦克跟我说了
Mike told me.
关于可卡因  孩子  坐牢的事
Right, the coke, the kid, jail.
我无法想象你现在有多难受
I can't imagine what you're going through.
我他妈被困在这个房子里了
I'm stuck in this fucking house.
我刚刚把卡尔的T恤按颜色整理好
I just organized Carl's t-shirts in color order.
简直快疯了
I'm going mental.
我都走不到人行道  警报就响了
Can't even make it to the sidewalk without bells going off.
我...
I, uh--
会不会有警察来找我
So should I be expecting a knock on my door?
为什么
What for?
可卡因是我的
It was my coke.
你就是为这个来的
That's why you're here,
想看看我是不是把你供给了警方
to see if I ratted you out to the police.
-同时也想看看你...  -操你妈
- And to check on you-- - Fuck you.
-到底有没有  -没有  你个混蛋
- Yes or no-- - No, asshole.
供出来就好了
I should have.
要是把你卖了还能早点出来
They would have let me off easier.
是吗  那你为什么没说
Well, yeah, why didn't you?
因为我讨厌自己的原因已经很多了
Cause I hate myself for a number of reasons right now
我不想再加一项出卖别人
and I'm not going to add being a snitch to the list.
-好吧  -你毁了我的生活  你知道吗
- Okay. - You ruined my life, you know that?
当着你们全家人的面
Dropping that little bomb on Mike
把事情告诉了麦克
in front of your family.
我那是帮你  好吗
I did you a favor, okay?
你的工作烂死了
The cup job sucks
我那兄弟又是个无聊到死的蠢货  对吧
and my brother's a boring yuppie asshole, all right?
我来了
Hey, girl.
抱歉让你等了这么久
Sorry I took so long.
都怪我肚子里这俩小妞
Got held up in the bathroom by the two girls in my gut
坐在我膀胱上影响我机体功能
sitting on my bladder blocking my functions.
我去  你这脸色真可怕
Damn, you look like hell.
是啊  一直睡不着
Yeah, I'm not sleeping.
还好我给你带来了"催眠饮料"
Good thing I brought over some snooze juice.
好了  慢点倒
All right, all right.
为了加快销售速度
We're accepting cash only offers
我们只接受现金
to expedite the sale,
所以价格定得比较低
which is why the price is so low.
契约文件都在我们的律师手里
Our lawyers will hold the money in escrow.
所以需要快点转手
We need to unload it fast.
要付两项抵押贷款太辛苦了
Paying two mortgages is killing us,
而且得给我爸找个暖和点的地方住
plus Dad needs to get to a warmer climate asap.
你看看他
I mean, look at him.
慢点  外公
Easy, grandpa.
我们想做一次全面改造
We're looking to do a renovation,
花费四个月的时间
a four-month turnaround.
价格会比定价低一点
We'll purchase under ask.
全部现金支付
All cash.
你跟哈希德那家人商量吧
Duke it out with the Hasids.
十分钟前刚跟他们谈妥
Put an offer down about 10 minutes ago.
长得挺瘦的  说不定你能打过他们
Skinny dudes. You could probably take them.
这个沙发可以买
This couch is for sale
那台桌子  电视也在卖
and that table and the TV.
这个椅子多少钱
How much for this chair?
你想出多少
How much you want to pay?
不如就给...
Well, how about--
只收现金  谢谢
Cash only. Please.
爸  成功了
Dad, it's working.
他们都信了
They're falling for it.
是不是很好玩
Isn't this fun?
你还好吗
You okay?
在为明天卡尔的事
I'm conserving my energy
储存体力
for Carl's thing tomorrow.
每支枪都上好膛了
Every gun's loaded, okay?
这是一支巨蝮XM15半自动步枪
So here we got your bushmaster XM-15 semiautomatic.
用的是镀铬枪管
Premium 16-inch chrome-lined profile barrel.
棒
Sweet.
这枪保护家人够用吗
What do you think about home protection?
我马上要有三个孩子了
I got three little ones on the way.
保卫家宅呀
Safeguarding the old homestead, huh?
《第二修正案》嘛[公民持枪]  老兄
Hey, Second Amendment, brother.
捍卫自由全靠枪子儿
Got to protect my freedom one bullet at a time.
好吧
Okay, so...
那就米尔科姆M32 MGL-140榴弹发射器吧
Milkor M32 MGL-140 grenade launcher.
够你捍卫自由的了
Protects a shitload of freedoms.
六发榴弹  双动扳机
Six-round cylinder, double-action,
军用级别武器
military grade weapon.
少了几个部件
Missing a few parts, but...
但还是能发射
it still shoots.
好重
It's heavy.
这家伙多少钱  说个数
What are we talking here? How much?
五千左右吧
Well, around five grand.
五千美元
$5,000?
-是的  -拜托  老兄
- Yeah. - Aw, come on, man.
球棒怎么卖
How much for the bat?
我勒个去
Holy shit.
我得走了
I got to go.
-我操啊  -就这样
- Holy shit. - That's it?
门卫
Concierge.
医学编码员  录音打字员
Medical coder. Transcriptionist?
我他妈都不知道这是些啥
I don't even know what half this shit is?
除了超级无聊以外
Other than supremely boring?
没人需要我了  小维
No one needs me any more, V.
黛比找对象了
Debbie's dating.
利普念大学了
Lip's in college.
卡尔在学校里惹了麻烦  我又帮不了他
Carl's in trouble at school and I can't help him.
谁知道伊恩又在搞什么
Who knows what's up with Ian.
他们都长大了  你还指望怎么样
They're all growing up. What'd you expect?
你也该考虑自己的需求了
Time for you to figure out your own needs.
技术支持人员
Tech support provider.
不够格
Underqualified.
翻译
Translator.
不够格
Underqualified.
-还有拍黄片呢  -太够格了
- There's porn. - Overqualified.
你干什么呢
Hey, what are you doing?
想办法在家赚钱
Finding ways to make money from home.
有什么东西烧焦了吗
Hey, is something burning?
-闻到了吗  -我操
- Smell that? - Oh, shit.
-我操  -操啊
- Oh, shit! - Shit!
天哪  妈的
Oh, my God. Oh, shit.
家里着火啦
Fire in the hole.
不是我家
Not my hole.
你就让它这么烧焦
You just let it burn?
我们在做其它事
We got distracted.
天呐
Oh, God.
你烂醉如泥
You're shitfaced.
什么时候加拉格家的人喝酒也成重罪了
Since when is a felony for a Gallagher to drink?
冷静点  这得怪我  酒是我带来的
Calm down. It's my fault. I brought the vodka.
你还灌她喝了吗
Oh, and poured it down her throat?
是你叫我放松的
You're the one who told me to relax.
谁他妈去把那玩意儿关了
Somebody shut that thing up!
操  就把房子烧了吧
Fuck. Burn the house down, okay?
也把食物烧焦
Burn the food too, you know,
我总能从半工半读的破餐厅
I can always steal some more
再偷点吃的回来
from my shitty work-study job, right?
我正在经历一段难熬的时期
I'm going through something here.
是啊  看样子你一小时
Yeah, it looks like you went through
"经历"了五瓶酒  菲奥娜
about five beverages in an hour, Fiona.
再来一瓶吧  为什么不呢
Have another one. Why not?
谁都管不了你
You're your own woman. Right?
睡了上司的哥哥
No, bang the boss's brother.
把可卡因放在孩子们够得着的桌上
Leave coke out on the table for the kids.
被逮捕
Get arrested.
你要做什么随便你
Do whatever the fuck you need to do.
家里我能照顾好
I've got this.
卡尔  上楼
Hey, Carl, go upstairs,
拿上牙刷还有睡觉的东西
get your toothbrush and something to sleep in.
他明天还要参加停学会议
He has the suspension meeting tomorrow.
别担心  不用担心
Oh, no worries. No worries.
我会及时送他去希拉家的
I'll get him to Sheila's in time.
我通宵学习
Stay up all night studying.
有什么关系
I mean, what the fuck?
不就是应用物理学测验嘛
It's just an applied physics quiz.
黛比在哪
Where's Debbie?
她在希拉家  跟萨咪一起
She's at Sheila's with Sammi.
-维罗妮卡  -在呢
- Veronica! - Yeah?
你怎么不接电话
You're not answering your phone?
我没听见  怎么了
I didn't hear it. What's up?
卡罗要生了
Carol. She's in labor.
什么  我去
What? Oh, shit.
祝我们好运
Wish us luck.
什么东西烧焦了
There's something burning.
-我们走  -不要
- Let's go. Come on. Go... - No.
拜托  利普
Hey, come on. Lip, please.
-你不用带走他们的  -是啊  我不用
- You don't have to take them. - You're right. I don't.
别这样  那晚餐呢
Come on. What about dinner?
你自己享用吧
Enjoy.
别响了
Shut up!
你的手指再敢靠近那条鸡巴
Those fingers go anywhere near that cock,
我就把你这只手的每个指节都打断
I'm gonna break every knuckle in your hand,
全部15个
all 15 of them.
别激动  好斗小子
Settle down, rumble fish.
不过一只手可只有14个指节哦
Anyway, a hand only has 14 knuckles.
你他妈找死吗
You want to fucking die?
我的一位常客请我们
We got invited to an after-hours
下班后去他的顶楼套房聚会
at the loft of one of my regulars.
很好玩的
It's fun.
好玩有什么不对
What's wrong with fun?
没有  除非涉及某个胖基佬
Nothing unless it involves some fat faggot
把脏手伸进...
shoving his hands down--
干什么  讨厌
No-fuck.
我总是在想他
I mean, I think about him all the time.
只要闲下来  他就会出现在我脑海里
Whenever my brain pauses, he just shows up,
就算是我不希望他出现的时候
even when I don't want him to.
你都想他什么呢
What do you think about?
他的头发  眼睛
Like, his hair, his eyes,
有时仅仅是他的名字
sometimes just his name.
这正常吗
Is that normal?
当然
Absolutely.
我的两个朋友  霍莉和艾丽
Because my two friends, Holly and Ellie?
她们总说  "男孩都很蠢"
They're always like, "boys are stupid",
还一副很厌恶他们的样子
and they act like they hate them.
但我从来没有这种感觉
But I never feel that way.
那你什么感觉
How do you feel?
挺奇怪的
Um, this is weird.
我感觉想去保护他
Like I want to protect him.
怪吗
Is that weird?
不  亲爱的
No, honey.
我还觉得头晕想吐
I also feel sick and dizzy.
坠入爱河的人都是这种感觉
Mm, that's how everyone gets when they're falling in love.
坠入爱河不是应该感觉很美妙吗
But I thought it was supposed to feel good.
是的  但有时
It does, but sometimes,
这种感觉实在太美好了
the good parts are so good,
你会愿意经受难以置信的痛苦
you're willing to suffer An unbelievable amount of pain
只为一尝这种感觉
just to get to them.
所以我才结婚三次
That's why I have been married three times
订婚十二次
and engaged 12.
那美妙感觉什么时候才会有
But when do the good parts start?
现在挺难的
Well, right now it's hard.
他把你甩了  改变了规则
He changed the rules a little bit by dumping you.
你现在最好呢
Best thing to do?
就是假装毫不在乎
Act like you don't give a shit.
要怎么做
How do I do that?
跟他一起玩
Well, hang out with him.
打扮得漂漂亮亮的
Make yourself pretty.
给他机会想清楚自己放弃了什么样的尤物
Give him the opportunity to consider what he gave up.
女人就是这样处理问题的
That's how a woman handles things.
那他就会把我追回去吗
And then he'll want me back?
你得耐心点
Have to be patient.
亲爱的  这可是长线作战
This is a long con, baby.
你要有必胜的决心
You're in it to win it.
坚持就是胜利
Stay the course.
明白
Got it.
谢谢你的建议
Thanks for talking to me.
我没办法找菲奥娜谈这些事
I can't talk to Fiona about any of this stuff.
她现在自己都顾不过来
She's a total spaz right now.
不过
But also,
我觉得她也很害怕孤独终老
I think she's afraid of ending up alone.
那是她该操心的
That's her shit,
不是你
not yours.
拉好了
All done.
来人帮忙擦擦  扶我出去
Need help wipin' and walkin'.
来了  爸爸
Coming, dad.
去去就回
Be right back.
对了
P.S.,
有个姐妹真好
I love having a sister.
是啊
Me too.
老弟  玩得还好吧
Hey, kiddo, you doing okay?
当然  大学都这样吗
Yeah, is college always like this?
问朗
Ask Ron.
我也没参加多少派对
Well, I don't party that much,
我尽量克制每天玩《我的世界》超过八小时
and I try not to play more than eight hours of Minecraft a day.
要是你在学校表现好点
And then you start doing better in school?
以后这些都是你的
All this could be yours.
大学真爽
College rules.
看看这地方
Check out these digs.
看看这夜景
Look at that view.
那家伙是干什么的
What does this joker do?
他是个工程师  还兼职摄影师
He's an engineer and part-time photographer.
我觉得这些照片有些就是他照的
I think he took some of these pictures actually.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
他为什么要让你来这里
Why'd he want you to come here then, huh?
别紧张
Oh, come on,
不是每个人都想占我便宜  米奇
not everybody wants something from me, Mick.
伊恩
Ian.
-你能来太好了  -莱恩
- So happy you could make it. - Ryan.
很高兴来来这里
Oh, good to be here.
这是米奇
Hey, this is Mickey.
幸会幸会
Delighted to meet you.
你俩有谁想喝鸡尾酒吗
Uh, could I get either of you a cocktail?
你这儿有啤酒吗
Yeah, you got beer?
我这儿有精啤  烈啤
I've got some craft brews, a stout,
印度爱尔啤酒  麦啤
IPA, winter wheat.
普通啤酒呢
How about beer?
当然  这有什么不可以的
Right. Could I be any more of a fag?
啤酒马上就来  伊恩你呢
One beer coming up. Ian?
我去看看都有什么
Let's see what you got.
你是新来的
You're new.
你和伊恩一起的
You here with Ian?
是的
Yeah.
他很不错
He's great.
你是做什么的
So what do you do for living?
做生意
I run business.
哪种生意
What kind of business?
服务业
Hospitality.
很好  什么方面
Oh, nice. What realm?
拉皮条的
I'm a pimp.
等等  真的吗
Wait, you're serious?
太棒了
That's incredible.
我的论文是关于变性人性工作
My dissertation is on transgender sex work
和妓女与嫖客
and symbolic interactionism
关系框架中的符号互动论
within the framework of hustler-client relations.
你有名片吗
You got a card?
晚安  小黛
Night, Debs.
晚安  弗兰克
Night, Frank.
莫妮卡
Monica.
晚安  菲奥娜
Good night, Fiona.
晚安  利普
Good night, Lip.
晚安  卡尔  伊恩
Night, Carl and Ian.
晚安  利亚姆
Good night, Liam.
到时间了
It's time.
我靠
Oh, shit.
要当爸爸了
Time to be a daddy.
等等  都生完了
Wait, what, we missed it?
为什么没人叫醒我们
Why didn't anyone wake us?
我不让他们叫
I told her not to.
我要一个人面对
I needed to do this on my own.
真是个小不点
He--he's--he's nothing.
又软又柔
He's just softness and goo.
小家伙
Hey, buddy.
我是你爸爸
I'm your daddy.
也是你姐夫
And your brother-in-law.
好奇怪啊
How weird is that?
为了闻到妈妈母乳的味道
You know, he did that little thing that babies do
他跟其他婴儿一样闻来闻去
where they can smell their mommy's milk,
我跟他说话的时候
and he could hear my voice
他能听到我的声音
when I was talking to him.
然后他躺在我的胸前
And then he laid up on my chest
找到乳头  轻轻地吮吸
and he found my nipple and he took a little snack.
妈妈你没事吧
You okay, mama?
我只是有点情绪化
You know, it's just a little emotional,
没事
that's all.
是不是我抱走得有点早
Did I take him too soon?
给你
Here you go.
这是外婆
Here's grandma.
他真是个
Oh, he's such--
真是个小天使
He's such a little angel.
这个小天使你们当时还不想要
He's an angel that you didn't want.
那只是个假设
That was hypothetical.
但他是我生的
But he came from me.
他是我的骨肉
He's part of me.
老天  妈妈
Jesus, mama.
对不起  我只是...
I'm sorry. I just--
我不知道自己会这样
I just didn't know I was gonna feel this way.
可是他...
But he's just--
他太可爱了
He's just so beautiful.
没关系的  妈妈
It's okay, mama.
你可以随时来看他
You can visit him any time you want to.
他是个小天使
He's a little angel.
小凯
Kev.
-凯文  -他是我的小天使
- Kevin. - He's my little angel.
小凯  她想留下孩子
Kev, she wants to keep him.
不行
She can't.
她不会放弃孩子的
She's not gonna let go of that baby.
她必须放弃
Well, she has to.
为了他  我经历了这么多
After everything I've been through with him,
他是我的  小维
he's mine, V.
小凯  三个孩子
Kev, three babies?
我不管
I don't care.
那是我的儿子
That boy is my son.
看着我
Look at me.
还有两个
There can be two.
还有两个漂亮的女孩
Our two beautiful baby girls.
她是个好妈妈
She's a good mom.
会做的很好的
She'll be great.
你看她把我养得多好
Look how well I turned out.
好吧
Yeah, well,
陪审团还在盯着这件事
the jury's still out on that.
我不想失去他  小维
I don't want to lose him, V.
他和妈妈就在我们身旁
He'll still be right there with mom.
他还是你的儿子
He'll still be your son.
你的孩子
Your boy.
她来抚养
Her responsibility.
放手吧  宝贝
Let him go, baby.
喂
Yeah?
我知道你不信任我
I know you don't trust me.
我知道你想惩罚我
I know you want to punish me,
我都明白
and I get it.
我也想惩罚我自己
I want to punish myself.
现在我没法向你或任何人证明
I have no way to prove myself to you or anyone.
但是  上帝呀  利普
But, christ, Lip, this, like,
这无止境的强烈负面能量
relentless passive aggressive bullshit,
要把我折磨疯了
it's killing me.
我需要我的家人  可以吗
I need my family back, okay?
求你了
Please?
别紧张
Easy, killer.
我是来问大家要吃什么早餐的
I'm taking breakfast orders.
炒蛋  松饼  还是法式吐司
Scrambled eggs, pancakes or french toast?
炒蛋
Eggs.
他呢  他要什么
And what do you think he'll want?
我他妈怎么知道
How the fuck should I know, man?
我又不是他的监护人
I'm not his keeper.
好的
Right.
我没别的意思
Didn't mean to assume.
那么...
So...
你们是昨晚才认识的吗
Did you guys just meet last night,
还是情侣
or are you together?
情侣
Together.
真棒
Cool.
你是个幸运的家伙
You're a lucky dude.
这就好了
There you go.
如花似玉
Fresh as a daisy.
看起来棒极了
You look terrific.
现在让我们去好好收拾他们吧
Now let's go knock 'em dead.
早上好
Good morning.
恕我直言  加拉格先生
Frankly, Mr. Gallagher,
您儿子的行为是我在这所学校
your son's behavior has been among the most egregious
见过最恶劣的
I've seen at this school,
而我已经在这里从教许久
and I've been here a long time.
肯定没超过三个月
Don't look a day over 90.
他恐吓这些学生
He terrorizes these students
令他们心惊胆战的来向我投诉
to the point that they move through my halls in fear.
学校不该是恐怖的殿堂
School should not be a palace of terror.
它该是学习的神庙
It should be a temple of learning.
孩子在让他们惶惶不安的地方
If children do not feel safe,
怎么能够学习呢
how can they learn?
他们不能
They can't.
她是在问我  小笨蛋
She's asking me, chipwich.
让卡尔认识错误的办法只有一个
The only way to get through to Carl
就是让他直面自己犯下的错误
is have him face the truth of what he's done
并从中吸取教训
and let him absorb it in a meaningful way.
快去  拜托
Do that, okay?
他不能这么随便
He can't just do it.
他得认真反省
He needs to actively engage.
-你有具体建议吗  -有
- Got any suggestions. - Yeah.
他应该向我的孩子和这里的每一个孩子道歉
He should apologize to my kid and every other kid here.
诚恳的逐个道歉
Individually. Like he means it.
别矫情了
Oh, spare us the wiener act.
霸凌是每个生态系统重要的组成部分
Bullying is a vital part of every ecosystem.
它教会小鬼如何从困境中站起来
It teaches kids resilience.
外面的世界很残酷
The world is a rough place.
霸凌是在给他们打预防针
Bullying is like getting inoculated.
就像种疫苗
It's a vaccine.
你们这些小兔崽子
And you little shit,
要学会离我儿子这样的恶棍远一点
you got to learn to stay away from people like my son.
被人往脸上抡了一拳
That's what you learn
就该学到点东西
when you get punched in the face by a bully.
你们以为史蒂夫·乔布斯是怎么成功的
How do you think Steve Jobs turned out so great?
就是被霸凌
Bullies.
我敢保证  你儿子
And I guarantee junior here
三十岁的时候身边一定全是辣妹
will be getting the hottest chicks when he's 30
因为他今天被霸凌了
because he got bullied today.
你想要你的孩子现在出彩吗
You want your kid to peak now?
我的孩子不出十年就会穿囚服
My kid will be picking up roadside garbage
在路边捡破烂
in an orange jumpsuit in ten years.
你的孩子会进医学院
Your kid will be in med school
治疗癌症  四处滥交
curing cancer and getting laid.
不用谢
You're welcome.
我要是也想治疗癌症怎么办
What if I want to cure cancer?
你没从狱友身上染上淋病
Be lucky you don't get gonorrhea
就算走运了
from your cell mate.
都是爱的提醒  儿子
Spoken with love, son.
回府
Home.
我太为你骄傲了  爸爸
I am so proud of you, dad.
恭喜你  兄弟
Congratulations, brother.
我们失去他了
We lost him.
天呐  出什么事了
God, how?
死胎吗
Stillbirth?
卡罗
Carol.
她要留下孩子
She kept him.
所以小孩没死
He's not dead?
没有
No.
只是不是我们的了
Just a little less ours.
我很抱歉  兄弟
Sorry to hear that, man.
但你还有两个嘛
But, hey, you still got two on the way.
我本来有四个的
I was supposed to have four.
我一直丢孩子
I keep losing babies.
如果有一颗俄国卫星
I mean, what if there was a russian satellite
把世界的通讯都切断
that took out all the communication in the world.
最后两个也没了
Two more babies gone.
或者什么变异病毒爆发
Or if there was a mutant virus
把我们都变成僵尸
that turned us all into zombies--
那是电影
That's a movie.
好几部电影
Several movies.
那又怎样  万事皆有可能
So? It could happen.
看吧  小孩改变了你的世界观
See, babies change your perspective.
到处都潜藏着危机
There's danger lurking everywhere.
我要开始搜集求生用品了
Now, I'm gonna start collecting survival gear.
罐头食品  药物
Canned goods, medical stuff,
对讲机  手电筒
walkie-talkies, flashlights.
我的格言就是
My motto?
早作准备
Prepare and prevent,
免得后悔莫及
don't repair and repent.
那是我的格言
That's my motto.
你不能独占一条格言  克米特
You can't own a motto, Kermit.
打死它  打死它
Get him! Get him.
它不见了  搞什么
Oh! He disappeared. What the heck?
两秒钟内它就会在你背后复活
He'll regenerate behind you in two seconds.
-转身  -不
- Turn around. - Oh! Oh, no!
它从后面叮到我了
Oh, he bit me in the back.
混蛋
Jerkface.
没礼貌
So rude.
真是的
Aw, man.
很高兴我们能继续做朋友
I'm glad we could stay friends.
是的  我也这么觉得
Yeah. Yeah, me too.
要不要一起去吃披萨什么的
Do you want to get a pizza? Or...
我也想  但我今晚还有个约会
I wish I could, but I have a date tonight.
要回家梳洗打扮一下
Got to go home and get cleaned up.
好的  当然了  没问题
Okay. Yeah. Yeah, sure. No problem.
一起出来很开心
But it was was fun hanging out.
是的
Yeah.
击个掌
High five.
再见
See you.
I'll see you.
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气
No problem.
那么  你学到了什么呢
And so what have we learned?
霸凌是社会的恶行
Bullying is bad for society.
它会伤害人们并且让他们感觉很糟
It hurts people and makes them feel bad.
霸凌必须被停止
It must be stopped.
很好
Very good.
我忘了带午餐
Forgot my lunch.
给我钱
Give me money.
给我钱  小狗崽
Give me money, chihuahua.
快点  给我钱
Come on, give me money.